karvymfs.com 2019-06-07

# ::Privacy Policy::

Privacy Policy  
---  

**Applicability**   
This privacy policy is applicable to the website www.karvymfs.com . We respect the right to privacy of everyone who visits this site. KFPL MFS is committed to protecting your privacy and working towards offering you an effective and safe online experience.  
However, users and viewers are informed that by using the web site www.karvymfs.com, they are deemed to have consented to the collection and use of information by KFPL-MFS as stated in the policy.   
  
**Information Collection and Use**  
  
To avail some of the services it may be necessary for you to provide us with details that personally identify you. Any personal information that you share with us, like your name, date of birth, address, marital status, telephone number, credit card particulars and the like, shall be entitled to privacy and kept confidential.   
KFPL MFS does not collect personal information about individuals except when such individuals specifically provide such information on a voluntary basis. Personal information of users of KFPL MFS website will not be sold or otherwise transferred to unaffiliated third parties unless we are legally entitled or required to do so or if we believe that such action is necessary to protect and/or defend our rights, property or personal safety and those of our users/customers etc or without the approval of the user as the case may be.  
While KFPL-MFS assures you that it will do its best to ensure the privacy and security of your personal information, it shall not be responsible in any manner whatsoever for any violation or misuse of your personal information by unauthorised persons consequent to misuse of the internet environment.   
By providing information through this site, you acknowledge and consent to the collection, use and disclosure of personally identifying information of the type and for the limited purposes as described in this Policy.  
KFPL MFS may collect unnamed statistics, which does not personally identify you. KFPL MFS reserves the right to perform statistical analyses of user behavior and characteristics in order to measure interest in and use of the various areas of the site.   
KFPL-MFS notifies that the information you provide to us may be transmitted and stored in a country other than where you reside for maintenance and any other purpose as may be permitted under applicable laws, rules and regulations from time to time.   
  
**Usage by minors**  
  
Karvymfs.com is not intended for use by children and minors. Parents are requested to ensure that personal information is not provided by minors on Karvymfs.com. However, this does not intend to prohibit information on minors and children being provided by the parents with respect to any service offered by Karvymfs.com or any other third party permitted to offer any product or service on its site, which are beneficial to or are designed for the benefit of children and minors.   
  
**Value of investments as stated on the site :**  
  
The value of your investment(s) as stated on the site is based on yesterday's published unit prices- (NAV) and unit balance currently recorded. The unit price shown may differ from the actual unit price for your investment due to change in NAV. The unit balance may not include recent transactions that have not yet been processed.   
  
**Use of Cookies**  
  
Users are also made aware that certain information and data may be automatically collected through the standard operation of KFPL-MFS internet servers or through the use of "cookies." "Cookies" is a term generally used for small text files a web site can use to recognize repeat users, facilitate the user's ongoing access to and use of the site, allow a site to track usage behavior and compile aggregate data that will allow content improvements, etc. Cookies themselves do not personally identify you, but they do identify your computer. You can erase or block this information by changing the settings on your computer. If you do erase or block this information you may not be able to utilise some features of the site.   
  
**Link to other sites**  
  
For your convenience, this page may contain certain hyperlinks to other sites. While we try to link only to sites that share our high standards and respect for privacy, we are not responsible for the content or the privacy practices employed by other sites.  
We recommend that you check the policy of each site you visit and contact the owner or operator of such website if you have any concerns or questions.   
  
**Newsgroups, Message Boards, Chats**  
  
KFPL MFS believes in promoting amity among users to promote collaboration and free exchange of ideas. At any time this site may offer chat rooms, message board facilities, newsgroups etc. During such activities, you may provide your personal information beyond what has been given in your personal profile. KFPL-MFS Privacy Policy excludes information transmitted through these activities. While KFPL-MFS encourages you to actively participate in such activities, it advises you to be careful in sharing your personal information and respect the privacy of its other users.   
  
**Data Security**  
  
KFPL-MFS has endeavored to take reasonable measures to prevent unauthorized access to and improper use of your personal data submitted to KFPL-MFS via your use of this site.  
KFPL-MFS shall adopt suitable measures to diagnose any problems with its server and to administer the web site Karvymfs.com including by blocking certain addresses that it feels are inappropriately using its website.  
  
**Changes in the policy**  
  
KFPL-MFS reserves the right to change this policy at any time. If KFPL-MFS decides to change this policy, such changes will be posted on this page as soon as possible. Users may note that this Privacy Policy itself and any such change of policy may be effective from the date announced by KFPL-MFS and not from the date of posting on the site.   
This statement and the policies outlined herein are not intended to and do not create any contractual or other legal rights in favour of any user or viewer of KFPL-MFS or on behalf of any other party.   
  
**Contacting Us**  
Karvy Fintech Private Limited   
Karvy Registry House  
"Karvy Plaza",   
H.No. 8-2-596,   
St.No.1 - Banjara Hills,  
Hyderabad 500 034 Email - [supportmfs@karvy.com](mailto:supportmfs@karvy.com)  
**Termination in case of paid subscribers/clients of KFPL MFS :**  
  
Either the user (paid subscribers or clients of KFPL MFS) or KFPL MFS may terminate this arrangement by either of them giving to the other 10 days prior notice in writing. It shall be on the discretion of KFPL MFS that the period of notice of 10 days may be waived or a shorter period of notice may be accepted in writing from the user.   
  
**Non-exclusive Remedy :**  
  
Termination or expiration of this arrangement, in part or in whole, shall not limit either party from pursuing other remedies available to it, nor shall either party be relieved of its obligation to pay all fees that are due and owing under this arrangement through the effective date of termination. Neither party shall be liable to the other for any damages resulting solely from termination as permitted herein.   
  
**Indian Law :**  
Any dispute, whatsoever, arising out of this arrangement shall be governed by the Laws of India. The Courts of law at Hyderabad shall have exclusive jurisdiction over any disputes arising under this arrangement.
